Register of the Baronessa Marii͡a Dmitrievna Vrangel' collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Part I (Boxes 2-38)
  - File 33, 1926-1933 (Boxes 36-37)
    - Miscellaneous organizations and community groups
      - Russkoe Studencheskoe KHristianskoe Dvizhenie (R.S.KH.D.)
        - Correspondence
          - Zernov, N., September 1928 (Box 36, Folder 26)
          - Zernova, S., September 1929-October 1933 (Box 36, Folder 27)
        - Miscellaneous material including brochures, catalogs and fund-raising leaflets, 1928-1932 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Russkoe Teosoficheskoe Obshchestvo, includes correspondence of A. Kamenskaia, Vestnik and other printed matter, 1931 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 36
      - Soiuz Russkikh Dvorian, Vestnik, No., 1-2, 1927-1931
      - Russian workers' organizations
        - Bulgaria, Pernik Mines, miscellaneous material, includes handwritten reports by A. Boltunov, memoir by Maj.-Gen. Liubimov, printed matter and map, 1925-1932 (Box 37, Folder 3)
        - France
          - Soiuz Russkikh SHofferov, miscellaneous material, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous material including correspondence with S. Gorodetskii and clippings, 1928-1932 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - File 34, 1931-1938 (Box 37)
    Miscellaneous memoirs and speeches.
    - Griunberg, O., memoirs, typescript, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Kliueva, Z.A., wife of Gen. Kliuev and subsequently Abbess Pavla of Russian Convent in Jerusalem
      - Correspondence, October 1931-July 1938 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Memoirs, including description of experiences as nurse in WW I and emigration, handwritten, December 1931 (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
    - Speeches prepared for Baroness Ol'ga Vrangel' by V. Davats, V. SHul'gin and others, typescript, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - File 35-36 (Box 38)
    General correspondence distributed in files above and miscellaneous unsorted clippins re émigrés and émigré life, 1920s-1930s.
    - Correspondence
      - Distributed in files above
      - General, 1920s and 1930s (Box 38, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 37
      - Clippings, miscellaneous, unsorted re émigrés and émigré life, 1920s-1930s (Box 38, Folder 2-7)
- Photographs (Boxes 39-49)
  - Lists of photographs, typescript, undated
  - File 37 (Box 39)
    Photograph albums depicting Russian Church abroad, Russian writers, academics and other prominent individuals.
    - Album 1. "Russkie Pravoslavnyia TSerkvi za Rubezhom i Dukhovnyia Litsa v Izgnanii". Miscellaneous photographs depicting Russian Orthodox churches abroad and portrait prints of clergy in exile, 1932 (Box 39)
    - Album 2. "Russkie Pisateli, Obshchestvennyia Deiateli i Uchenye v Izgnanii". Includes portrait prints of writers: Prince V. Bariatinskii, N. Berberova, I. Bunin, B. Zaitsev, G. Kuznetsova, M. Osorgin, V. Nabokov, A. Remizov and S. Remizova-Dovgello, Teffi, V. KHodasevich, V. Nemirovich-Danchenko, A. Kuprin, G. Ivanov, N. Odoevtseva and others. Also includes portrait prints of individuals prominent in social organizations and community affairs and Russian academics abroad, 1920s-1932 (Box 39)
  - File 38 (Box 40)
    Photograph albums depicting artists, musicians and actors.
    - Album 3. "Russkie KHudozhniki v Izgnanii, ". Includes portrait prints of A. Benois, F. Brailovskaia, L. Brailovskii, S. Vinogradov, I. Bilibin, D. Stelletskii, R. Verhovskoy, M. Dobuzhinskii, I. Repin, N. Roerich, G. Lukomskii, K. Somov, V. SHukhova, V. SHukhov, N. Globa, Z. Serebriakova, A. IAkovlev, B. Grigoriev (includes informal family snapshots), N. Bogdanov-Bel'skii, A. SHchekhotikhina, S. Tereshkovich, T. Kossinskaia, T. Rodzianko, N. Sofronov, M. Rundal'tsev, K. Beklemisheva; group photographs of Russian artists at "Mir Iskusstva" exhibit in Paris, 1921 and "Obshchestvo Ikona", Paris, undated, 1917-1931 (Box 40)
      Available on microfilm reel 38
    - Album 4. "Russkie Muzykanty i Artisty Baleta za Rubezhom, 1932". Includes S. Rakhmaninov, I. Stravinskii, N. CHerepnin, N. Metner, A. Ziloti, S. Prokofiev, F. SHaliapin, S. ZHarov, A. Pavlova, B. Nizhinskaia and others, 1925-1932 (Box 40)
    - Album 5. "Russkie Artisty, Drama i Kino", 1930s (Box 40)
  - File 39. Reau, Louis et al., Boris Grigoriev, Faces of Russia, London, 1924 (Box 41)
    Printed matter, Boris Grigoriev.
  - File 40. Farrère, Claude et al., Boris Grogoriev, Bouis, Bouis, Petropolis, 1924 (Box 41)
  - File 41 (Box 41A)
    Photograph albums depicting Russian military abroad.
    - Album 6. "Russkaia Armiia v Izgnanii. Gallipoli, ", 1920-1921 (Box 41A)
  - File 42 (Box 42)
    - Album 7. "Kazaki." Lemnos. Includes portrait prints of Lieut.-Gen. F. Abramov, Maj.-Gen. Lobov and Col. P. IAsevich, group photographs of cossacks at work, in training, recreation, embarking on transport ships to Balkans and at work in Bulgaria, 1921-1922 (Box 42)
    - Album 8. "Kazaki v Izgnanii". Includes portrait prints of Gen. A. Kaledin, Gen.-of-Cavalry Krasnov, Gen. A. Filimonov, Gen. A. Bogaevskii, Maj.-Gen. SHil'nikov; "Donskoi Kadetskii Korpus v Serbii"; group photographs of Kuban' and Terek units and miscellaneous other photographs, 1918-1932 (Box 42)
    - Album 8a. "L'Armée Russe au Travail dans les Balkans, ", 1922-1923 (Box 42)
    - Album 8b. Same as Above, 1924 (Box 42)
    - Album 8c. "L'Armée Russe en Exil, ", 1926 (Box 42)
  - File 43 (Box 43)
    - Album 9. "Russkaia Armiia v Izgnanii, ". Includes portrait prints of White military leaders, 1921-1932 and miscellaneous photographs depicting "Russkii Velikago Kniazia Konstantina Konstantinovicha Kadetskii Korpus" (Serbia), 1920-1932 (Box 43)
    - Album 10. Same as above. Includes photographs depicting Drozdovtsy and Markovtsy, 1918-1929 (Box 43)
    - Album 11. Same as above. Includes photographs of Russian army units at work in Pernik Mines and other locations in Bulgaria; Russian officers at work in Germany and France (Foreign Legion); miscellaneous photographs depicting officers of Russkie Invalidy za Rubezhom, 1924-1931 (Box 43)
  - File 44 (Box 44)
    Photographs depicting funeral of Gen. P. Vrangel'.
    - Album 12. "General P.N. Vrangel',", 1914-1928 (Box 44)
      Available on microfilm reel 39
      Includes official photographs of Gen. P. Vrangel' as military leader, informal prints of him and his family, and photographs depicting his funeral.
    - Album 12a. Perenesenie Prakha Generala Vrangelia v Belgrade 6 Oktiabria 1929 g. (Box 44)
      Printed copy. Photographs depicting funeral of Gen. P. Vrangel'.
    - Album 12b (Box 44)
      - 6 Oktiabria 1929 v g. Belgrade
      - Bolezn', Smert' i Pogrebenie P.N. Vrangelia v Briussele, undated
  - File 45 (Box 44)
    Miscellaneous photographs depicting émigré life abroad.
    - Lepta Artillerista, Nos. 1-4, 1921
      Magazine has not been microfilmed.
      Hand-produced magazine. Includes memoirs, literary work, statistical information, and original illustrations, Gallipoli and Orkhanie.
  - File 46 (Box 45)
    - Album 14. "Leib Kazaki s 1917 po 1933,", 1917-1933 (Box 45)
      Includes Civil War, Lemnos, and Serbia, 1917-1924.
    - Album 15. "Leib Kazaki s 1917 po 1933,", 1917-1933 (Box 45)
      Includes Cossack life and work in France, 1924-1933.
    - Album 16. "Snimki iz Russkoi ZHizni Prezhnei i Sovremennoi,", 1881-1932 (Box 45)
      Album has not been microfilmed.
      Includes group photographs of the Imperial Family (Alexander III), Russian Military Staff WWI, dedication of Russian memorial church in Bulgaria (King Ferdinand of Bulgaria); Vrangel' family photographs; portrait prints of leaders of White Army in Far East; Don and Kuban Cossacks in exile in Bulgaria; Don Cossacks in France; portrait prints of Russian scientists, academics, doctors, individuals active in community affairs, painters (Larionov and Goncharova in Paris). Miscellaneous prominent individuals (S. Petliura, S. Perovskaia in rare informal snapshot, 1881, informal snapshot of "Anastasia" CHaikovskaia).
  - File 47 (Box 46)
    - Album 17. Russian emigration in Czechoslovakia, includes individual and group photographs of religious and intellectual community in Prague, 1921-1928 (Box 46)
    - Album 18. Same as above (Box 46)
    - Album 19 (Box 46)
      - Russian emigration
        - Australia, 1927-1931 (Box 46)
        - China, Harbin, includes "Russkii Dom", 1922-1924 (Box 46)
        - Korea, undated (Box 46)
        - Morocco, undated (Box 46)
        - Serbia, Belgrade, includes "Pervaia Russko-Serbskaia Gimnaziia v Belgrade", 1934 (Box 46)
  - File 48 (Box 47)
    - Album No. 20. "Russkaia Emigratsiia v CHekhoslovakii", includes group photographs of organizations, funerals of N. and K. Kramarz, 1930s (Box 47)
    - Album No. 23. Russian Imperial Family, including pilgrimage to Sarov, informal snapshots of life in "Belovezhskaia Pushcha" and Empress Marie Fedorovna in exile; illustrated uniforms of Russian Imperial Army; informal print of Lieut.-Gen. P. Skoropadskii; Baron P. Vrangel' in uniform of Guard's Cavalry; Col. Oleg Pantiukhov; photographs of Pushkin family, 1890s-1936 (Box 47)
  - File 49-50 (Box 48)
    - Album 21, 22. "Russkaia Emigratsiia v Bel'gii", 1930s (Box 48)
      Available on microfilm reel 40
    - Album 24. "Russkaia Emigratsiia v San-Frantsisko 'Zhivaia lietopis' zhivykh' Arkhiv Baronessy M. D. Vrangel" (Russian Emigration in San Francisco), 267 pages, 158 photographs. Album compiled by Ephim Pavlovich Beliaev, 1920s-1930s (Box 49)
- Part II (Boxes 50-59)
  Miscellaneous material re Russian émigré life, arranged according to place of residence. Mostly printed matter.
  - Europe
    - Austria (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Report, handwritten, 1929
    - Belgium
      - General
        - Miscellaneous typescript, handwritten and printed matter re Russian emigration, 1920s-1930s (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - "Baian" Musical Firm, programs, including M. TSvetaeva and S. Rachmani, nov, 1930-1934 (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - "KHram-pamiatnik v pamiat' TSaria-Muchenika Nikolaia II", printed matter, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - "Russkaia Strelkovaia Druzhina", miscellaneous typescript and printed matter, (No. 50), 1930-1936 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
      - Biographical material. Miscellaneous short autobiographies of Russian émigrés residing in Belgium, typescript and handwritten, includes material re Pushkin family, 1927-1937 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
        Available on microfilm reel 41
      - Visual material
        - 13 prints depicting Russian students at Université de Louvain, also miscellaneous postcards of Belgium, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Bulgaria
      - Miscellaneous typescript, handwritten and printed matter, 1928-1930 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Visual material. Postcards of Bulgaria and signed portrait prints of politically prominent Bulgarians, Miscellaneous photographs of Russian émigré community, including schools in Varna, group photographs of officers, arrival of refugee ships and former military personnel at work (Balabanov Factory and others), 1921-1930, 1920s-1930s (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 42
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1929-1933
      - Printed matter. Russkie v Prage. 1918-1928 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Visual material. Postcards and informal photographs of Russian students in Brno, 1920s (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Danzig
      - Reports, handwritten and clipping, 1929-1930 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Denmark
      - Report of Lieut.-Gen. S. Pototskii, typescript, 1928 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Estonia
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1929-1931 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Printed matter. Russkii Kalendar', 1931 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Finland
      - Corresponence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1932 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - France
      - General reports and clippings, 1926-1930 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Charitable organizations: correspondence, reports, clippings, typescript and handwritten, 1923-1932 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Printed matter, Russkii Almanach, 1931 and Otchet po Soveshchaniiu russkikh ispol'shchikov i arendatorov na IUgo-Zapade Frantsii 16-18 fevralia 1929 v Tuluze (Box 53, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 43
      - Visual material. Photographs of "Russkii Dom" and miscellaneous postcards, 1930s (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Germany
      - Miscellaneous material including report re émigré life in Berlin (1922). Also see correspondence with Lieut.-Gen. A. von Lampe and others, typescript, 1922-1930 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Printed matter
        - Doklad, Soiuz Russkikh Evreev v Germanii, Berlin, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Rabinovich, I., Russkie v Germanii IUridicheskii spravochnik, 1920 (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - S.IA., Spravochnik dlia russkikh v Berline, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Visual material. 17 photographs, mostly postcards but some informal snapshots of Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Great Britain
      - Report, typescript and clippings, 1928-1930 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Visual material. Miscellaneous postcards of the royal family, 1920s (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Greece
      - Reports, correspondence and clipping, typescript, handwritten and printed matter, 1927-1929 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Visual material. Postcards and group photographs of Russian émigré community in Greece, 1920s (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Holland (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Letter and clipping, 1928-1929
    - Hungary
      - Reports, typescript, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 44
      - Visual material. Photographs depicting gifts presented to Gen. P. Vrangel', undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Italy
      - Miscellaneous material, including correspondence and report of Prince A. Volkonskii, handwritten and typescript, 1929-1930 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Visual material. Postcards, including royal family, Mussolini and Pope, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Latvia
      - Correspondence with Prince A. Lieven and V. Markozov, report re Russian emigration in Latvia and list of Russian organizations, handwriten and typescript, 1928-1930 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Printed matter. Russkii Natsional'nyi Soiuz v Latvii, Ustav and Otchet, 1924-1931; Rizhskoe Blagotvoritel'noe Obshchestvo, Ustav and Pervoe Piatiletie, 1928; Rizhskoe Russkoe Prosviatitel'noe Obshchestvo, Otchet, 1929; miscellaneous clippings, 1921-1930 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Lithuania
      - Correspondence and reports: M. Apraksin, IA. Fedorov, G. Gritsevich, M. CHepinskaia, handwritten and typescript, 1929-1935 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Visual material. Informal snapshots of Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Luxemburg
      - Report on work in "Ideal" Factory, Wilts. Informal photographs of Russian workers at factory, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Norway
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Visual material. Postcards, including royal family, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Poland
      - Golenko, M., "Posledniia tsarskaia okhota v Belovezhskoi Pushche v godu", handwritten, 1935, 1912 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1931 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Visual material. Informal photographs, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Spain
      - Correspondence and clipping, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Rumania
      - Correspondence and report, handwritten and typescript, 1928-1929 (Box 55, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 45
      - Visual material. Postcards, including royal family, 1920s-1930s (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Switzerland
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings, typescript and handwritten, includes material re legal status of Russian refugees, 1928-1931 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Printed matter. League of Nations reports, 1920-1928 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Sweden
      - Correspondence and reports of D. Kandaurov, handwritten, 1928-1930 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Visual material. Postcards of royal family, 1920s (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Turkey
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings, typescript and handwritten, 1920-1930 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Visual material. Russian refugees on Island of Antigone, 1920-1921 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Yugoslavia
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1922-1931 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Printed matter. Panchevskii Gospital'-Sanatorii R.O.K.K., 1920-1930; Russkii Dom Imeni Imperatora Nikolaia II, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
      - Visual material. Postcards, including royal family and group photographs of KHar'kovskii ZHenskii Institut, 1920s (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Asia and the Middle East
    - Afghanistan and Bukhara (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 46
      - Postcards, 1920s
    - China
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1929-1931 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Memoir. Bezobrazov, S., re Civil War, handwritten, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Printed matter
        - Russkii Delovoi Spravochnik po SHankhaiu, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - Clippings, 1929-1930 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Visual material. Photographs of Shanghai, 1920s (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Goa
      - KHabarov, V., correspondence and "Zavoevanie Indii", printed copy, 1928-1930 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - India
      - Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Visual materials. Postcards of Belgaum and snapshots of Russian émigré life, 1920s (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Iran
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1930 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Iraq
      - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 47
    - Java
      - Correspondence, N. Petrushevskii, 1928-1932 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Visual materials. Informal prints of N. Petrushevskii, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Japan
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1933 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Visual materials. Group photographs of Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Palestine
      - Clipping and postcards, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Philippines
      - Letter, Postcards, 1920s, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Syria
      - Correspondence, reports and clipping, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1930 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Visual material. Photographs, including Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Africa
    - Abyssinia
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1928-1929 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Visual material. Photographs of royal family, military groups and Russian clinic, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Algeria
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1929-1930 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Congo
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1929-1932 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Visual material. Miscellaneous snapshots, including Russian doctor at work, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Egypt
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1922-1930 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Visual material. Miscellaneous snapshots, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Madagascar
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Morocco
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1929-1932 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Visual material. Postcards and group photographs of Russian Foreign Legionnaires, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Sudan (French)
      - Correspondence, D. Trubetskoy, September 1931 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Tunisia
      - Correspondence and clippings, typescript and handwritten, 1928-1932 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - North America
    - Canada
      - Correspondence and reports, typescript and handwritten, 1929-1932 (Box 58, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 48
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - United States
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings, 1928-1932 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Printed matter. Russkie v Amerike. Polnyi Russko-Amerikanskii Spravochnik, 1931 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - South America
    - Argentina
      - Correspondence and clippings, 1928-1936 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Bolivia
      - Correspondence and report, handwritten and typescript, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Brazil
      - Correspondence and reports, typesript and handwritten, 1928-1931 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Printed matter
        - Russkaia Gazeta, 1928-1931 (Box 59, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 49
        - Clippings and advertisements, 1929-1931 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Visual material. Postcards and photographs of Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Costa Rica
      - Correspondence and photographs, August 1933 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Paraguay
      - Correspondence, reports and clippings including report re revolution of, 1936, 1930-1936 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Visual materials. Postcards and photographs of Russian émigrés, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Peru
      - Report, typescript, and clipping, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Uruguay
      - Correspondence and reports, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Printed matter. Clippings and advertisements, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Visual material. Photographs of Russian émigré community, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Australia
    - Correspondence, reports and memoirs, handwritten, 1929-1930 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Visual material. Postcards and photographs of Russian émigrés at work, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii
    - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - New Zealand
    - Correspondence and reports, handwritten, 1928 (Box 59A, Folder 15)
    - Visual material. Postcards, 1920s (Box 59A, Folder 16)